[
  {
    "question": "What happens to a frog's car when it breaks down?",
    "button": "What?",
    "answer": "It gets toad away."
  },
  {
    "question": "What's brown and sticky?",
    "button": "What?",
    "answer": "A stick."
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you count cows? ",
    "button": "How?",
    "answer": "With a cowculator."
  },
  {
    "question": "What did the blanket say when it fell of the bed?",
    "button": "What?",
    "answer": "Oh sheet!"
  },
  {
    "question": "Whatâ€™s the best thing about Switzerland? ",
    "button": "What?",
    "answer": "I don't know, but the flag is a big plus."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did the scarecrow get promoted? ",
    "button": "I dunno, why?",
    "answer": "Because he was outstanding in his field."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did the tomato turn red?",
    "button": "I can't imagine",
    "answer": "Because he saw the salad dressing!"
  },
  {
    "question": "What did one snowman say to the other snowman?",
    "button": "What?",
    "answer": "Do you smell carrots?"
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you call a fish with no eyes?",
    "button": "No idea",
    "answer": "A fsh."
  },
  {
    "question": "What time is it when you have to go to the dentist?",
    "button": "No idea",
    "answer": "Tooth-hurtie"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why are pirates so mean?",
    "button": "Why?",
    "answer": "They just arrrr!"
  },
  {
    "question": "How to you wake Lady Gaga?",
    "button": "How?",
    "answer": "Poke 'er face."
  },
   {
    "question": "Why do teenage girls hang out in odd numbered groups?",
    "button": "Why?",
    "answer": "Because they can't even."
  }, 
  {
    "question": "Where do you find a down-and-out octopus?",
    "button": "Where?",
    "answer": "On squid row."
  }, 
  {
    "question": "What's the easiest way to catch a fish?",
    "button": "Tell me",
    "answer": "Have someone throw it at you."
  },
  {
    "question": "What's that gooey stuff in between a shark's teeth?",
    "button": "Eww, what?",
    "answer": "Slow swimmers."
  }
]